[sensual music]
[moans]
[sensual music continues]
Does it have to be from behind?
[Elisse] Andrea.
Elisse! Um...
Sorry. Uh, no, uh...
I just received these rushes.
There's a complaint from a talent.
So I had to check her poses.
Her hip was aching.
So, I just... You know.
- What can I do for you?
- Mmm...
SAM.
- Oh.
- [Elisse] I want to talk about SAM.
Okay.
[in English]
I just really want to spend
as much time as I can with Felize.
[in Filipino] I want to...
[clicks tongue]
I want to...
cut down on my workload.
I'm sorry.
I've decided that
this is how it should be.
Of course, I understand you. Come on.
But what about your income?
Well, I'm not really...
quitting, no.
- [Andrea] Okay.
- But...
I'm gonna have to be more picky.
- I'll say "no" to some projects.
- Mm-hm.
Like... I'm passing on
Juan Makabayan.
I won't do it anymore.
Actually, I think that, maybe,
this is not a good time
especially since SAM's closing down.
[playful music]
Hm...
Oh, my god, Deo. Oh, I'm sorry.
Deo, this is the absolute worst.
Chin, how was the Portrait shoot?
- Why?
- I'll report to Ms. Andrea.
Of course you will.
I was there until dawn
because Maricel and Snooky
did nothing but bicker.
One refused to go to the set
and the other wanted to go home.
Really?
They were okay when I was there.
Are you saying it's my fault?
That I can't control them?
No, I don't mean it that way.
Do you have a problem with me?
Have I done something?
Why would I have a problem with you?
[Sofie] Camille.
Let me through.
Ms. Andrea says
she needs to talk to you later.
And Sir Matthew told me
to tell you to help Noemi
with the documents for the meeting
with Ms. Helen.
Okay.
It seems like I'm not needed here.
Maybe I can go home and rest.
Or is there anything else I need
to report to you, Ms. Camille?
What was that about?
[cell phone ringing]
[Chin] Sorry.
Hello.
Didn't I say that I'd call?
I just wanted to commend
your good work, and...
Maybe you can ramp it up a bit more?
Make it a little bit faster.
What?
Sir, you know how tough it is
keeping our secret.
[Paul over phone]
Yes, but that promotion I'm offering
should get you all fired up.
- [Joseph] Oh!
- Hi, Joseph!
What's up?
What are you doing? Loitering again?
Look, I'll see what I can do, sir.
Your agency is on its way down!
I'm sure you've heard
about Matthew's daughter, right?
I have, sir.
See that? If you don't move on,
they're going to take you
down with them.
You don't want that, do you?
[Paul over phone]
Do you know who's the first
celebrity you're going to manage
when you sign up with us is?
Roderick Paulate.
The Box Office King! See?
Let me show you just how Galaxy works
how we manage our stars
how we make the most
out of every situation
so we can get the best out of them.
You'll see.
I don't care about the private lives
of these celebrities.
I don't even care that they're
a bunch of stupid divas in real life.
As long as they bring in the money,
then I will love them.
I will take care of them
and we will make the most
out of them.
But the moment they fail to deliver,
then it's goodbye.
It's goodbye.
And you know what you call that?
You call that good business.
That's a little harsh,
don't you think?
Are you with me?
Okay, sir, but I have to go. Bye!
My god.
[theme music]
♪ Careful, careful ♪
♪ The world is full
Of jealous people ♪
♪ When envy strikes,
It means trouble ♪
♪ That's why we need to be careful ♪
♪ Careful, careful ♪
♪ We always need to be careful ♪
♪ Prying eyes ready to snoop ♪
♪ Digging for the juiciest scoop ♪
♪ That's why we need to be careful ♪
♪ Careful, careful ♪
Eventually, Maricel and Snooky
got back to work
and finished all their
scheduled scenes for today.
[Andrea] Yeah,
and what about Zsa Zsa?
I heard she's leaving us.
You know already? That was fast.
So you told your dad?
It was Noemi who told him.
Another news.
Elisse is cutting back on work.
She's away from her kid too long.
So now I bet everyone thinks
all my talents are problematic.
I tried my best with Ms. Zsa Zsa.
Maybe you didn't explain it well.
[Andrea] In the first place,
you're always working with Karylle
but you still haven't fixed this?
May I remind you
that I'm the one who hired you.
Prove to me that I made
the right decision in hiring you.
And again, you work for me.
Not for Matthew, for me.
Yes, ma'am.
Now, if you really want
the junior manager position,
then do your job.
Fix the Karylle and Zsa Zsa thing.
- You heard me?
- Yes, Ms. Andrea.
Okay. My script.
Go.
[inquisitive music]
Sorry! Sorry.
Do you need anything, Noemi?
No. Just go on.
- [awkward chuckle]
- Wha... Why?
Who are you messaging?
- Karylle.
- Aah...
Just Karylle? No one else?
I mean, why?
Ms. Andrea told me to find a way
for Karylle and her mom to make up.
- Is there something wrong?
- No, nothing's wrong!
Nothing. Thanks!
Thanks!
[inquisitive music]
- [Chin] Did someone text me?
- [Noemi gasps]
[cell phone ringing]
Hello, yes, Sir Gab. Mm-hm.
I'm in the pantry. Okay, on my way.
- Later, Noemi.
- Mm!
[cell phone pinging]
[tense music]
Need anything?
[tense music intensifies]
[inaudible dialogue]
[Noemi shrieks]
- What happened?
- What was that?
Excuse me.
What was that?
What happened?
- Are you okay?
- Uh...
[awkward chuckle]
Sorry, I thought
there was a cockroach.
[all] Huh?
- What a waste of time.
- You're weird.
What a huge cockroach!
Are you okay?
[Noemi] Yeah.
That was some scream.
We heard you all the way here!
It sounded like murder.
I thought there was
a flying cockroach.
- A cockroach?
- It's just a pin.
How can that look like a cockroach?
I'm not sure, I'm not really sure.
- Hey, Sofie?
- Yeah?
Can you put everything here?
Ogie Diaz's videos
the leaked stories about Brandon
and about Rob.
There's more.
[Sofie] Now everyone knows
about Ms. Zsa Zsa and Karylle.
I have no idea how they found out.
They even know about SAM closing.
[frustrated sigh]
Maybe Karylle's name
was mentioned on YouTube
or maybe someone's snitching.
I really don't know.
What will you do?
I have to find out who that spy is.
This mess is just getting bigger.
And I will not stop
until I discover who it is.
Okay, I'll gather everything
right now.
[knocking on door]
[Gab] Andrea.
[Andrea] Come in!
I'm here!
Why is it so dark?
- [Andrea clears throat]
- I'm so hungry.
Oh!
Another costume party?
Just trying a few things on.
Come! Sit!
Wait.
I'm really hungry. You hungry?
[Andrea] Come on!
Here I go.
I just remembered.
You said the spy
could be one of us in SAM.
But I think...
that's impossible.
I mean...
Remember when you told me
I don't need anything
or anyone to have a baby?
Right, you can do it on your own.
Apparently, I do.
[moans]
- You do?
- Uh-huh.
What?
[playful music]
How about it?
Why me?
Who else?
- Who else? Come on.
- What do you mean "who else"?
- Come...
- [Gab] Hey!
Stop it. Matthew!
He's made two babies already!
- [Andrea] I know!
- I only have one kid!
No! His is too old,
and it might not work!
- I want you!
- How about male exes?
Come on, please!
No way, I'm going home!
Hey!
I'm going home.
- Sit. Stay!
- I am not sitting!
I need just that!
You're being selfish!
- You've given away a lot...
- The heck?
...but you won't give me some?
Are you drunk?
- Come on!
- [Gab] No way!
[Andrea] It'll just be quick, right?
Let's do it!
- Help!
- Just close your eyes.
I'm still a woman! Don't be choosy!
I swear I'm gonna hit you!
- Please!
- I said I wanna go home!
- Let's get this over with!
- [loud thud]
[Gab] Ouch! That hurts!
[Andrea] Selfish jerk.
Fine, keep your sperm!
- [Gab] Is this blood? Is it mine?
- [Andrea laughs]
I changed my mind.
This is too tough. Some other time.
You've slept with men before, right?
Yeah, but I didn't enjoy myself.
Just like I didn't enjoy
having to seduce you.
Hey, no means no, even for me.
You pushed.
And now you're insulting me.
[chuckles]
Can I tell Matthew?
- Please no.
- Come on!
He needs a good laugh!
Wow. You mean he's still depressed?
Yes. He's really down.
And you'll use me for a laugh?
No sense in letting
that costume go to waste.
It's cute, though.
But you know...
there are things in my life
that I can't lose.
I wouldn't survive without them.
[Andrea] There's my mom, of course.
Top of the list.
Well, of course, granted
she's not really there anymore.
But you know, she's just there.
I'll still take what I can get.
And of course I can't lose you.
Like I can't lose SAM.
So this baby thing...
I'll have to park it for now.
There's just too much
we need to do for SAM.
- I'll get to it one day.
- Okay.
Okay. Can you put on a jacket now?
You believe him?
[Brandon over phone] I told you.
[in English] I don't want to pay
for any breach of contract.
If Galaxy can talk to our brands
and fix this mess
why should I not let them?
[in Filipino] Brandon,
you still have a few more months
on your SAM contract.
I know.
[in English]
That's why I'm telling you now.
- [dial tone beeping]
- [clears throat]
[in Filipino] What do we have today?
[in English] That's a list
of our Social Media Division clients
their current endorsements,
and other obligations.
[Matthew in Filipino]
What am I looking at?
I can never understand those numbers.
[Noemi] These are just comparatives
to avoid conflict of interest.
[in English]
Speaking of conflict of interest.
Where did you get that?
[in Filipino]
Is this your solution, Matthew?
This is what you meant
when you said "I'll take care of it?"
Well, if you're leaving us
now tell me, how the heck
are we gonna buy SAM?
Calm down, Andrea.
I haven't signed anything yet.
- [Andrea] Yet?
- He hasn't decided!
And you knew about this?
You didn't even bother telling me?
And you dared to look me in the eye
and tell me I could trust you.
How dare you!
Wait! What is happening?
Matthew? You're moving?
To Galaxy?
Not before I fix our problems.
Give me that! This one.
Give it to me!
This is our biggest problem.
This!
Guys, can you step outside?
No! Let them freaking stay.
[Andrea] Let them know
and hear us say it.
That there will be no junior manager
no more Social Media Division
and no more artists to manage
because there will be no more SAM!
[dramatic music]
Chin.
- Chin! What did you just do?
- What do you mean what did I do?
You and I are the only ones
who saw that contract.
You told me not to tell Ms. Andrea!
- You told me not to get involved.
- Because they are going to fight.
And I was right!
[Chin] Why does it sound like
you're accusing me?
You were holding
your father's contract.
You're the one who left it.
Why are you blaming me?
This is not the business
for friendship.
This isn't college or high school.
It's the toughest place
to find someone to trust.
I've been in this business
for a long time.
I've met so many people.
But friends?
I could count them on one hand.
Real friends are hard to find here.
[in English] It's not what you think.
I've been trying to hold off
making this decision
for as long as I could.
You should have told us.
[in Filipino] There's no way
we can buy SAM on our own.
Let's not talk about this now.
[in English]
We have to talk to Helen first.
What are you planning to tell her?
[in Filipino]
That she can sell SAM to someone else
because we don't have
the money to pay for it?
[in English]
Is that what you're saying?
You just have to trust me.
You're making it very difficult
to trust you.
You lied about Paul,
you lied about Gina
you lied about living here.
About Camille!
And who knows what else?
You know...
it may not seem like it now...
but I'm doing this for you.
- I'm doing this for Samuel.
- Oh, no.
Don't you dare...
Don't you dare say that.
[mouths] Don't you dare.
- [Gab] Hold on.
- [Andrea] Don't you dare.
[cell phone ringing]
- [Gab] What do you even...
- Wait.
It's Helen.
No one comes to see me.
I don't pull up ratings anymore.
WE LOVE YOU
But...
But!
KEEP FIGHTING!
- I want to thank...
- [notification pings]
...each and every one of you
for all those years.
All the love and support
that you've given me all these years.
Thank you very much.
- Ms. Karylle?
- Yeah?
- ...but I just have one request.
- Ms. Eula, excuse me. Thank you.
- Look.
- Is that Mama?
- For all the years you have given me
- Is it live?
all that love and support...
Please give it
wholeheartedly to Karylle.
Helen.
[in English]
We just want to know where we stand.
Helen.
Please don't sell SAM to Paul Amir.
Galaxy doesn't deserve SAM.
[in Filipino] Samuel...
would claw his way out of the grave
if he knew this would happen.
What has this got to do with Samuel?
He would never sell SAM
if he were alive.
But he's dead.
I'm surprised you weren't aware
that Galaxy is out of the picture.
[in English]
You were this close to losing SAM.
[Helen] And I'm selling SAM...
to you.
Oh...
[in Filipino] I was going to call you
tomorrow anyway
to discuss the documents.
[in English]
Whatever has to be signed.
And the check, of course.
[Helen] I'll give you one week
to pull the money.
[in Filipino] So...
you told Paul
you were moving to Galaxy...
Thank you so much.
[Gab] ...if he withdrew his offer
to Helen.
He would have stopped at nothing
until Galaxy was number one.
I hate you, Matthew.
Darn you.
[in English]
He's really bent on taking us down.
Matt.
Thank you.
Don't touch me, Andrea.
You really hurt me.
I know.
[in Filipino] But you know me.
I'm sorry you got caught in my anger.
I'm sorry.
Please.
- [laughs]
- What?
I'm not angry.
I just wanted to see you
beg me for forgiveness.
I hate you!
[all laugh]
So we're good?
- We sure are.
- Yay!
We sure are.
- You're so annoying.
- [Gab laughing sarcastically]
- Aren't you?
- It's not that funny.
Where do we get the money?
You know...
Gabriel, use your head, will you?
[scoffs] Wow.
No one else is buying SAM except us.
- Mm-hm.
- I mean...
Helen was wrong, you know.
No one else would want SAM
more than us.
I agree.
So whatever happens, happens.
The only concern now
is the money, but...
That's a piece of cake.
Whatever will be, will be.
[upbeat music]
[in English] Hello, everyone!
Good morning! Where are my boys?
- [in Filipino] Upstairs.
- Good!
Deo, what's happening to your face?
Are you having a stroke?
Let that flow! Rainfall is lucky!
[in English] Good morning, boys!
- How are my boys today?
- [Gab] Good morning.
- Good morning, thank you very much!
- Coffee all around!
- Wow!
- Are you guys ready to work?
[Andrea] Let's get to work!
- Oh, I'm so happy!
- No more coffee for you.
You might pull
your bunny act on Gabriel again.
Don't worry, you're next!
- [chuckles]
- Anyway...
Are you guys ready to work today?
I feel so positive today.
I'm pitching
our social media strategy
to my new talents.
So where's the energy here?
[thrilling music]
Yeah, Sofie mentioned it.
We'll take care of you, Lao.
Influencers!
We haven't forgotten
what you did for Laurice.
[Andrea] Yes, Elisse.
- We got you.
- It's perfect for you.
Lav's been working on this for years.
Hey, Andrea! Influencers!
Yes.
Sir Gab, did you like it?
Hi, Janine!
Yeah!
Well, about your renewal contract.
What's going on?
You never got back to me.
Is that from HBO?
Um...
We're working on it!
Just working out
the schedules with them.
So the project is still a go?
I heard about Rob.
Of course, it's a go!
Actually, we're done with casting.
[scoffs]
Call me when you have
the HBO contract for me to sign.
[in English]
Until then, I'm a free agent, okay?
- [Janine over phone] Bye, Andrea!
- Wait!
[Andrea over phone]
Hear me out first, okay?
Something's in the works here at SAM.
And we're building
social media content
for our artists.
And I think this is
a very good platform for you.
Um...
I can see you getting brands,
more brands!
A lot of endorsements!
- See?
- Wait, did you say social media?
Yes, social media
is the way to go, apparently.
You know, times are changing...
True!
Like weren't we just talking about
a lead role in a Hollywood film?
Times really are changing,
right, Andrea?
[grumbles]
- Good night, Ms. Andrea.
- [Andrea] This still isn't fixed?
That's crazy. Get it done!
- [Gab] Andrea.
- What?
Let's go. Drinks.
We need to unwind. Relax.
Yeah, a drink before bedtime
would be great.
So I won't have to listen
to him snore.
Maybe I'll fall asleep a lot sooner.
- Oh, really.
- No, I'm going home.
- Just a drink!
- We won't be long!
I said no! I want to go home.
You go.
That's an ugly jacket, burn it.
[in English] She's back.
It was fun while it lasted.
[in Filipino] Whoever they are,
the source of the leaks
they're really good.
What are you doing?
Taking a snapshot
so I can find it quicker.
[gasps]
Here we go!
What's that?
[Sofie] A charm!
[squeals, giggles]
I like it!
Pretty!
Looks good, huh?
[inquisitive music]
[Andrea] If Maricel
and Snooky leave...
[Ogie] ...wanted to take over SAM.
- [Gab] Frank Villacin!
- [Ogie] Karylle, Zsa Zsa.
- [Mr. Fu] Rob Gomez.
- [Ogie] Lav Diaz and Monsour.
[Mr. Fu] What did Rob do
to deserve this?
[line ringing]
Hello?
Uh...
I know where the leaks are from.
Why is Daisy here?
[gasps] That's okay, I'm not busy.
How about a snack? I brought palabok.
Noemi, what is this?
Do you not have a life?
[Daisy] Have a snack.
Um...
We have to talk.
Is this some kind of intervention?
Sort of.
We're not friends enough for that.
It was you!
You leaked all those rumors
about SAM!
[shrieks]
You?
You did that?
- [Sofie] Noemi.
- [Daisy] Oh, gosh.
- [knocks on door]
- Don't even try...
Camille, we're all sleeping here.
Sorry, Valerie.
[Chin] We're sorry.
- Daisy, shut up.
- Shut the door.
[Sofie] You're too loud.
No way, it was you?
Really, sis?
- What are you talking about?
- [Noemi] Don't deny it, Chin.
That picture
of Maricel and Snooky fighting?
You were on the set that day.
And so was Camille.
But they were not fighting
when I was there.
You know about Zsa Zsa and Karylle
and Brandon's issues too.
And even about SAM closing.
You all know about that!
That bedazzled phone is yours!
[Noemi] We saw its reflection
in Rob's picture at the hospital.
Okay.
So what are you going to do?
Are you going to gang up on me
and beat me up? Come on.
- [Chin] Come on.
- Don't be overdramatic.
How could you do that, Chin?
- I don't owe you any explanation...
- [Camille] I meant to Rob.
How could you do that to Rob?
I'm not doing anything wrong to Rob.
I didn't do anything to him.
I just wanted everyone to know
what Frank Villacin did to him.
Because none of you cared enough
to do that for him.
And what about the other leaks?
I wanted a promotion.
[Sofie] You think
that will get you promoted?
Not in SAM.
You're leaving?
Noemi...
you've been with SAM for so long.
[Chin] You can do your job
with your eyes closed!
If Matthew calls in sick,
you can easily do his work for him.
I can't compete
with the boss's child.
That has nothing to do with work!
Says the nepo baby!
Nepo baby?
No matter what I do...
I'm overlooked and underappreciated.
What are you talking about?
That's not true.
Sir Gab always tells me
he can't do any of this without you.
[Sofie] You should have
talked to him first.
Or us!
Chin, we're in this together!
[Noemi] We started nearly
at the same time.
We panicked and were stupid together.
We were both new, don't you remember?
And now you're leaving like this.
You're with SAM, Chin.
If you want this promotion so bad
you can have
the junior manager position!
Oh, please.
I don't care for handouts.
I'll leave you two
to wrestle for it, because...
I'll be a manager at Galaxy.
[Daisy] What?
- Are you ready to be a manager?
- Daisy!
Uh...
I just meant it's a difficult job!
It's tough work to be a manager.
Maybe I don't care.
I know for sure
you're all telling on me.
No worries.
I'll speak to Sir Gab tomorrow.
You won't see me again after that.
Chin!
I'm leaving.
- I'll borrow some cash for my fare.
- [Noemi] But...
That's my cab fare, Chin!
[Daisy] What's up with Chin?
What will Sir Gab say
when he finds out
this is all Chin's doing?
[knocks on door]
- [Karylle] Mama?
- [knocking continues]
It's open.
[relieved sigh]
You didn't tell me you were coming.
Mama.
What are you doing to yourself?
I don't know, K.
I just feel so alone.
[sobs]
I worked so hard
to give you everything.
But it seems I've given you nothing.
Mom.
Listen to me.
I'm not your fan.
I get it.
No, you don't.
I'm not a fan who disappears on you
when she finds someone new to stan.
I'm not a fan who's here today
but gone tomorrow.
I'm your daughter.
I will always be your daughter.
I am not the enemy.
But I'm not you either.
When I sing, I don't need
everyone else in the stadium
to sing along with me.
If I write a song
I don't need the album
to go triple platinum or something.
But in everything that I do...
know that
I want to make you proud.
[somber music]
[sobs]
Can you forgive me?
[chuckles]
[clacking]
Why are you here?
Deo's fixing a leak
near Sofie's desk.
It's too noisy for me there.
Chin...
You're wrong about me.
You're wrong about Sir Matthew.
And Ms. Andrea.
And Sir Gab.
You know them well.
Our chances for junior manager
are even, Chin.
Chin, I'm sorry.
It's my fault that you don't like me.
I didn't tell you
that Sir Matthew is my dad.
Our relationship started with a lie.
Maybe if I told you when we first met
it would be easier to trust me.
But really...
it was me who didn't trust you guys.
I didn't think you'd understand
that I really wanted
to work here at SAM
and be with Sir Matthew.
I love SAM, Chin.
That's why I'm doing my best.
I'm not here to compete with you.
Don't leave.
If you really can't stand me,
then I'll leave.
I'm tired.
Ever since I started working
I've always had to prove myself.
I ended up doing crazy things...
just so people
would take me seriously.
How do I not leave SAM now, Camille?
This is my biggest mistake ever.
Come on now.
I'd rather mess up here
than anywhere else.
I'm so far from my real home
but SAM is my home and family here.
Not just because of Sir Matthew.
It's because of you guys.
If I mess up
and Ms. Andrea screams at me?
I know you guys care enough about me
to give me a chance
to make up for it.
Sorry, Camille.
Did you tell him?
Tell me what?
Camille's right.
No one has to know.
You only have to tell them one thing.
Huh?
[upbeat music]
Oh, man.
I've messed up a lot of times.
But I don't dwell on my mistakes.
I fix them
erase them
and make them all right.
[in English] Tomorrow is another day.
Tomorrow is another chance
to make things right.
[in Filipino] I checked everything.
There is no one source.
There is no leak.
There are too many people involved.
The gossips are just so good
at what they do.
They're so good at weaving
all the information into stories.
Instead of looking
for the source of the leaks
we should just help our artists
deal with the rumors.
We do that so well.
We've done it before for Ms. Laurice.
Let's reclaim social media
and use it to our advantage.
Good!
Next question.
Throughout your stay in SAM
what has been
your biggest challenge so far?
I just can't say no to anything.
I'm always grumpy when I'm tired
or when there's too much work to do.
No matter how tough it is.
But no matter how mean I get,
I make sure I'm pretty.
Ms. Andrea.
I don't know her too well yet
so I make a lot of mistakes.
[in English] What do you think
are your best assets?
[in Filipino] I love my talents.
I'm a good teacher.
I'll do anything for them.
An ex-coworker said to me...
"Why should I mentor you?
Nobody taught me when I started."
I got out of there real fast.
Here in SAM, we're a family.
If one of us messes up,
it's everybody's mistake.
I'm here to teach my family
how not to mess up.
[in English] And I thank you.
[in Filipino]
Are they grilling Chin? How is he?
I'm sure he's fine, don't worry.
- [Noemi] Well?
- He's alive, thank god.
I think I did okay.
It's all good.
Thank you, girls.
Thank you. I'm really sorry.
It won't happen again. I promise.
- Mm...
- Mm-hm.
Group hug!
[all giggle]
[announcer in English]
Presenting the talented nominees
for this year's highly anticipated
Screen Spirit Awards.
This year's nominees
for the Screen Spirit Awards
Best Actor are...
Sir Roderick!
[in Filipino]
They're announcing the nominees!
[announcer in English]
Joel Torre for Celebes.
Rob Gomez for When Love Calls.
And Roderick Paulate
for The Lonely One!
Not really news when it's a given.
- Congrats, sir!
- Thank you!
The nominees for the Screen Spirit
Awards for Best Actress are
Lotlot de Leon for The Sacrifice.
Maricel Soriano for For Alida.
- Thank you!
- Mm.
Snooky Serna for Sabel's Secret.
And Lynette Marie Vicencio
for Amihan and I.
[Camille] Congratulations, ma'am!
Who's that other nominee?
I knew it! You were only listening
for your own name.
That one has nothing on you two.
That's Willy Wu's latest girl!
The producer?
The producer!
And the producer of all of her films.
So that's why.
Mother Aleta's Last Wish
is nominated for Best Picture.
SAM co-produced that.
Wow.
SAM has a lot of nominees.
Too bad you're closing shop soon.
[Roderick] Okay, back to work!
Hey, what's this light doing here?
Take it out!
Looks like my Aunt Metring
will get a job soon.
What is SAM doing
about all these rumors?
What are you doing about this?
Yeah, what's being done?
I think the director needs you
on the set.
Evasive maneuvers, huh?
- Whatever!
- It was just a simple question.
[Andrea] Yes, Zsa Zsa, don't worry.
Our RMs are doing their jobs.
Yeah. By tomorrow, I promise you
that video will be gone from YouTube.
I'll update you, okay? Bye.
Her decision's final.
She's leaving us.
[Gab] And Brandon?
He'll talk it over with the missus.
- You told him not to believe Paul?
- Yeah.
Missus? They were just fighting.
But this is about money.
That's the only time they'll talk.
Money, they agree on.
Speaking of money
I don't have any.
That's not news.
That's all I have
and it won't even cover my share.
Any word from the bank?
Nothing.
They said they'd call.
But you know, guys, we really have
to check on SAM's assets
or we'll never hear from the bank.
At least our application is there.
Oh?
Where's the energy
and the optimism, boys?
Where's our mantra?
"We own SAM, SAM is ours!"
Right?
"Right, Andrea?"
- "Yes, SAM is ours."
- [knocks on door]
[Andrea] Come in.
There's someone here to see you.
No appointment?
[Sofie] No.
Oh, well, might as well see them.
Could be a future client.
- [grunts]
- Let's go.
You should stay here, Sir Gab.
- Wait, why?
- Why?
It's Frank Villacin, he's downstairs.
[tense music]
I can't see him.
I know. We'll stay here.
Just sit. Sit down.
- [clears throat]
- Oh.
[Frank] Oh?
Aren't there three of you?
Where's the other one?
[in English] I'm sorry
no smoking.
No smoking.
[in Filipino] Even for visitors?
Yes.
These ceiling leaks are really bad.
We can file a complaint.
I know the City Engineer.
He can assess the damage
and we can sue the building owners.
I send him all the complainants
on my show.
[gasps] Sorry, that's broken.
[Andrea in English]
So what do you want, Mr. Villacin?
[in Filipino] Call me Frank.
[in English]
Okay, to make a long story short
I want Shine Artist Management...
to manage me.
Is this some kind of a joke?
[Frank] As you may know
I'm running for public office again.
But that's still six years away.
And I want to be prepared.
I want to start now.
Frank You is a top-rater.
[in Filipino] I have many followers
lining up for help at my office.
People come to me for help.
And I help all of them.
Oh, yeah.
But not before you make them fight.
That is what my viewers
and listeners want.
[in English] We're not publicists.
[in Filipino]
Our job is managing talents.
[in English] But you know what to do.
And you have the machinery.
[in Filipino] Sorry, that's expired.
Does anything still work in here?
You guys are good.
That thing with Rob Gomez?
You did a good job
of keeping that under wraps.
[in English] How dare you.
[in Filipino] Me?
I just got that off...
of Cristy's vlog.
So...
[in English] I don't know
what you're talking about.
[in Filipino] But if I did...
have something to do with that...
It's in the past.
We're even, and life goes on.
Let me sweeten the deal.
[in English] Agree to my terms...
and I'll pay you good money.
Why SAM?
Why us?
Because you're the best.
And that's the only kind
I want on my team.
[in Filipino] And I want to serve.
[in English] I can serve you.
[in Filipino] I may just be...
the help you need to keep SAM afloat.
Actually, I am all you need.
[in English] You know, um...
I'm sorry, Mr. Villacin.
[Matthew] You'll have to go
somewhere else.
We here at SAM...
We'll talk about it.
We'll get back to you.
There's no way I'm managing
the career of that criminal!
[in Filipino]
Andrea, he's a criminal.
[Gab] That's all he is!
It was just a thought.
We don't have to do it.
Or I can manage him myself,
you don't have to be involved.
[in English] That's crazy, Andrea!
Yes, thank you very much!
That is crazy!
You were there.
[in Filipino]
You saw what he did to Rob!
[suspenseful music]
[inaudible dialogue]
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[sobbing]
[panting]
Where's Rob?
[Rob] Chin...
Chin!
[sobbing]
No! Poor Rob.
I can't do a thing for him.
- And Andrea is talking crazy.
- Sir Gab.
Sir Gab.
Gabriel.
[Sofie] Rob is young.
He'll get over it.
Okay?
And this is Rob.
He knows what's important.
His family is important.
He'll get through this for them.
And he has his SAM family.
He has us. He has you.
He has Gabriel who takes care of him.
The Gabriel who is always there
for his talents.
He'll get through this.
He will never be alone.
Okay?
What if he leaves SAM?
Don't think that way.
But if it happens...
we move on.
We have no choice.
What is it?
Are you sure you wanna be an actor?
I think you'll make a great manager.
What?
[chuckles]
Me?
If it were just me...
this would be nothing.
But I have a family to think of.
Then you can do this, right?
For your family.
[exhales sharply]
Will you really quit acting?
Maybe I can go back to the province.
Taxes are way lower there.
[chuckles]
You know, Chin...
I made one small mistake...
and I'm ruined forever.
Hey, why are you crying too?
I made a mistake too.
I did you wrong,
but I didn't mean to.
- I'm so sorry.
- Chin...
I can't imagine you doing any wrong.
You don't understand.
If you knew what I've done and said.
Chin.
Whatever it is...
You can forget about it.
Everything you've done for me...
trumps anything wrong you did.
Thank you.
Come here.
[in English] Well, look who's here.
[in Filipino] How are you?
[in English] Not that I care.
[in Filipino]
That's just my standard greeting.
But I'm a decent woman,
so I'll ask you to sit.
[Aleta in English] Thank you, Helen.
Helen.
[in Filipino] We're too old to be
pulling each other's hair, aren't we?
[scoffs]
Well...
Don't you have questions for me?
About me and Samuel?
Nothing.
I no longer care about that.
[in English] It's all in the past.
All the memories I have with Samuel
include you.
[in Filipino]
Why would I want to relive that?
He's the one who left me, Helen.
[in English] I don't believe you.
He would've left me for you
the minute he had a chance.
[in Filipino] And he had his chances.
But he didn't leave you.
It's because he loved you,
that's why he stayed.
This is good news, right?
I mean
if they're asking us for all this
maybe they're considering
granting us the loan?
- Mm-hm.
- Right?
- [knocks on door]
- [sighs] Come in.
Ms. Andrea, this just came in.
Thank you.
Camille, can you call everyone?
- [Camille] Okay, ma'am.
- [Andrea] Thank you.
Wait.
We're making another announcement?
Why should we if we can't buy SAM?
Why not?
We still have a week.
Anything can happen.
Exactly.
Matty's right.
Anything can happen.
With that being said
I think you should handle
all the paperwork and requirements.
You know how this goes,
you'll get it done properly.
[sighs] This isn't over yet.
We're not going down without a fight.
[Andrea] As you all know
SAM is nominated in many categories
in the Screen Spirit Awards.
So me, Gab, and Matt
have decided to make it a party!
[all cheer]
And just so we're clear,
everyone is attending!
[screams]
Including me?
[overlapping excited chatter]
- Okay, hold on.
- [Camille] Chin.
- Here are the invites.
- There we go!
Please take one and pass it around.
[overlapping chatter]
[Andrea] Kids...
...take care.
- See you tomorrow.
- I'm an actor!
[Matthew] Hey, wait!
Come back, everyone.
Come back.
- We owe you one last thing.
- Oh, right.
[Andrea] If it's up to you...
If you were to make a choice...
Aside from yourself
who do you think should be
the new junior manager?
Right! We've decided.
- And after careful deliberation...
- Mm-hm.
Please welcome
your newest junior manager...
Um...
[drum rolls]
Noemi!
[all cheering]
[indistinct dialogue over cell phone]
Shh, listen!
[congressman] ...70 Yes, 11 No.
Two inhibited, one abstained.
The resolution to deny ABS-CBN's
franchise application
is hereby adopted...
Pursuant to Section 49 of the...
What? What did they just do?
- [cell phone ringing]
- [overlapping clamor]
Yeah, Zsa Zsa, I know...
[Gab] Yeah, we just heard it.
[Matthew] We just heard.
Breaking news.
Who voted?
[Chin shrieks]
[Gab] I'll call you back.
- [Andrea] Hold on.
- [Chin] Wait.
- [Camille] I'm very sorry.
- [Chin] I'll get a lamp.
- [Matthew] Don't hang up.
- [Gab] Where's Deo?
- [Camille] We lost power.
- [Andrea] What happened?
[overlapping chatter]
[Gab] Hey, look.
Is it just us having a power outage?
- Huh?
- Are you serious?
- [Andrea] What?
- It's just us.
Yeah.
What's happening?
Darn it.
[closing theme music]